https://www.paintball.co.uk/privacy-policy/

/privacy-policy/ Call fos
020 3869 9341
Call Now Call Now Book Online! OrBook Online!MENUHomeCentresAbout+Day ItineraryAbout UsGame ZonesEquipmentFAQsPlayers+KidsAdultsStag & HenTeam BuildingSchool & YouthPricesFind a Centre
OR Select VenueBerkshireBirminghamBristolBromleyBuckinghamshireCardiffCheshireColchesterCoventryCrawleyEast GlasgowEdinburghEssexGloucestershireGuildfordHertfordshireKentLeedsLeicesterLiverpoolLutonManchesterNewcastleNorthamptonshireNottinghamPlymouthReadingRomfordSheffieldSouthamptonTunbridge WellsWest Glasgow
From£14.99
From£14.99
Home / Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis website www.paintball.co.uk is owned and operated by BPE Limited of Suite 3415, Jardine House, 1 Connaught Place, Central Hong Kong. This website is the principle gateway for customers making paintball reservations.TopicsWhat information do we collect about you?How will we use the information about you?MarketingAccess to your information and correctionCookiesOther websitesChanges to our privacy policyHow to contact usWhat information do we collect about you?We collect information about you when you contact us and/or book a paintballing event with us. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies.How will we use the information about you?We collect information about you to process your order, arrange your event and, if you agree, to email you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you.We review user behaviour information collected from the website to improve the experience for you and other visitors to our websiteIf you agree, we shall pass on your personal information to our partners so that they may offer you their products and services.www.paintball.co.uk will not share your information for marketing purposes with companies outside of our group of partners.In processing your order, we may send your details to fraud prevention agencies.MarketingWe would like to send you information about products and services of ours and other companies in our group which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date.You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to our partners.If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please contact us as outlined at the bottom of this page.Access to your information and correctionYou have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the following address. We may make a small charge for this service depending on the nature of the request.We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurateCookiesCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.Other websitesOur website and electronic communication may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.Changes to our privacy policyWe keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 20 October 2018.How to contact usPlease contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:Email us at admin@bpelimited.com 020 3869 9341
UKPBA UK Paintball Association 5 Star Accredited Venue
Privacy PolicyTerms & Conditions
